Hi, my name is manassas and here I have my colleague lynne
...with me and what we're going to talk today about is vision services
...just-released as part of project oxford which
is announced a couple of days ago and what I'm going to talk about today is how you can take
...beautiful image like the one you're looking at the screen and
interpret and provide data which is very interesting and you can use it in your applications?
Just to remind everyone that it's every
it's that we should evaluate the session...the end.
The agenda for today I'm just going to briefly talk about what are the challenges and
why understanding images is very important and then I'm going to show you a
bunch of demos and then talk about the details of the api the...api summer talk about is
analyze I made which is basically and image processing service
which takes an image and gives tells you a lot of interesting information about the second one is
ocr which takes an image with text and converted into machine
usable text and the last one is which is one of my favorites which
is generated thumbnail which is you take an image...smart cropping?
So, the challenges of a modern app therefore challenges of a modern app the
first is that the images have become front-and-center of all applications
and this is very critical in because of the cost
...the transmission of data has become cheaper and,
that's the kind of the main reason the second is that most of the images are coming from a
variety of sources you building...the images are being submitted
by a third-person and you have to ensure that the images clean it
is appropriate for others to see the other aspect is you want to know something about
the image if someone is taking a photograph and...image it'd be good to know some aspects
...other humans in it other animals and...very
interesting and then once you have an image how do you presented beautifully how you
can you take advantage of the features of the image itself and present pres
...application better the third challenge
offer modern app is that you want to process instantly so as soon as
you have your mobile app or you have an app you want to instantly process these images.
the last is that you as a developer want to focus on your core value proposition
off of your app and not worry about
many expensive things of which and image processing algorithm may do.
So, how do we go to help you so this we
...microsoft as a research company has been investing in image processing
...vision and deep learning for many years and this combined with the
query click...of bing basically in bing...search we get
a lot of queries and we get a lot of if image results and people click on those results that
...graph is a huge training data which we can combine that
microsoft research to provide these services so what we...the services
...providing today are part of project
...which I'll talk more about and the across platforms...you can use them from ios
an android as well and...into the details of all the all of these three services?
Before I get into the details I just want
to should talk a little bit about one of our customers so this is one of a launch partners this is
picket dot me and what they are building is a marketplace where they want to connect people
...supplying images for with people who media
images as you can imagine the process thousands of images every day?
What are the challenges they have the challenges they have is they want to
build enhance search and browse experience for that they want to
understand the metadata which is in the image the second is that...the only choose appropriate
colors so that the butte this can beatified the...if the haven't image if they could if they knew
what the colors to show on the on the side or when the images loading which is the
right color to show in the background darby great and most importantly one of the reasons
they're using as is the ad when images a submitted they want to make sure that people
...us submitting anything in appropriate and they want to filter them out there's another and,
I'm going to show how we're going we're helping...me and all of this cases another customer
scenarios a very famous sports team...are working with
what they're doing is they want france to upload images in real-time and they want
to put it on facebook...on...on their side and
the what they want to do is they want to make sure that none of the images which are submitted
...would it wouldn't be appropriate for others to see
and that and that's the reason they're working with us
...dual-use...service of the company is a very famous wildlife company
they're building a wildlife app and for them it's very important when they get
images is that they want images with knowing the on a separate images that have humans with no
him animals especially so they want to keep all the animals...separately and then human
...separately and that for them is very and a very important aspect?
this would be a good time I think to show a demo to show our services.
So, this is a demo of our service so, for example,
if you had an image or let's start with the image whichever showing you earlier of the person
swimming so,what would we do is like we look at this image and a lot of
interesting things about it one of the things would be what this images in this case we identify that it's
neither clip art and online drawing which means it's a photograph and this is also very useful
the lot-of graphic sites which want to distinguishfor actual photographs from
non photographs another aspect is whether it's black-and-white or has a particular
color in it whether it's adult a racy I'll talk more in detail about what is addled
...racy later on?
And, then the other aspect is categories so in this case it recognizes that this images about a person
swimming.
We also recognize that zs there's one person in this image
...mail and,
we try to estimate is...and I'll talk more about it there's lot of talk about this
...in the internet a about this particular feature...
the colors dominant colors...dominant colors means what is the most important cullen this image and accent
...what is a contrasting color let's take this photograph of the new york
...in this case we recognize that this image is about buildings it's about
city and the...outdoor city and it's obviously a black-and-white image so
the colors are not very interesting and also...no people in it.
Let's take
another image this flower image so in this case
colors become very interesting so we identify all the dominant colors the most dominant
colors white here the black is a second-most and green is the third and the
...dominant color foreground is white and background is y and then
accent color is the contrasting color so which would want to be the most contrast
...and that's the pollen in the flout itself you can even go to
the side right now and even try a personal images so,
for example, let me.
...had a vacation to mexico so I
try I took some photographs over there and this one...the recognizes that it's
...it's a photograph of ocean and also that there is some stone...which makes
it very interesting...me being brave enough to hold a
lion and recognizes my age and my daughter's agedoesn't recognize my
son's age because he's looking a bit sideways and, it also gives...
contrasting color for this image which I'll talk more about later on which are the leaves in the picture?
And, you can if everybody's looking from straight ahead like in this photograph all the faces
...captured much better in this we can capture everybody's age young
and old this...a good time to go back to the dec.
And, let me talk a little bit more about some of these details about this
okay so we're talking about the first I'll talk about category detection which
...showing a so you could go to the side and try all of these
images oregon try and you any of your image and we will be able to recognize you know,
the categories whether it's ocean or sky or
the train station or whether it's a food image?
In general what we have done is we have trained our models using bing
data on eighty-six categories these are a prototypical categories photograph
others are interested in categorizing the photographs, for example,
for object we sub categorize...food and transportation and
bring animals and within animals cats and birds and dogs and
for outdoor another top-level...have categories like field
in ocean city how these and these are all very useful categories?
And, this same technology is internally used in microsoft for the one
...search which was recently released the and as the one-price...
and bing image its image source has been using it for a while and we measure
...quality on a standard photograph...dataset from mit and
...on that set...we do pretty well ninety five percent precision and
seventy-three percent recall what it means is that about three-fourths of the images in that dataset
we are able to...some category in it and, the position is pretty high.
So, the that's about category detectionlet me move on
...a different area.
What I'll explain this one by showing?
...bing if you go and type in line you see this beautiful of pictures of
...and you did a bunch of filter's here and one of the
filters ...type and you could say that I wanted to see only clip art photographs
...a...or you wanted to see only the line drawings of
a line also that there are color filters which
happens identify which are the colors dominant color of...you could
...color enriched showed those pictures of...or you could click on black-and-white.
So, what we're doing is we're exposing all of these things as part of
this service so-if you...if you if you submitted a picture of just like the one I have on the screen
you would get this happens to be a clip art and within
...we also say that is high-quality or...have a rating of from zero to...is know
...one is ambiguous...is the average...quality and
high-quality and then this happens to be a line drawing and this happens to be a black-and-white image as well?
And, these models
are more recall focused so we don't vid even if
...are a little bit ambiguous we and at...estimate them to be clip art line drawing and
black-and-white as I said before this is very useful for...couple of companies are working which they want
to distinguish photographs from non photographs and in those case it can be very useful.
This the next topic I...talk about is one of my favorite topics which is accent
...this is a common problem you have is you have this photograph of a
gentleman and you want to decide what should be the best contrast color
for this image and denotes if you are brave enough you would you'd go for of with
a bright color like a blue or red or most people are very,
you know, they would over the if you are building...website...typically go the neutral color
is one of the to bottom colors and would say those are safer colors I would go
with and this feature we released as part of windows eight and I'm going to show
...what's in windows eight which will give the inspiration?
Sofa in windows eight if you
...if you go to thisthe start screen and you type in a query like
...swift what you'll get is a
you got a beautiful hero image of her and followed by her news articles and
...albums and the color which you want to choose for the background here for the new than
...iswe is uses the same service and the way we
chose this color is by looking at which is the most
...popping color of the image which and which would be which will
...with the most contrasting color and in this case it happens to be her lipstick so does the
how lipsticks color widgets been chosen as the accent color and it helps
the whole screen to look more harmonious and I pleasing so let's take another example to make
this point more clear this is another query of...beyond
...you do a query...say and this cut in this case the color which was chosen
the blue-collar which has been chosen is the most saturated color
behind in our background and this color helps the screen look
you know, much more again, my very I pleasing and makes
...make...makes it flow much better this and this doesn't make the whole
application look boring otherwise what happens is you just have one color the background
you choose that consistently just to make this point even more
...this more complex example where ...reading...has very
different colors on her in this picture the color we have chosen is the color
...because that is the most contrasting color and makes the
screamed, you know, look, harmonious?
And, also we what we do is we try to avoid skin tone so...we don't use
skin tone is kind of avoided otherwise again this algorithm...work as well.
So, that there are two kinds of colors the exposing in this service
dominant an x and color dominant is very straightforward to understand
is what we do is we look at which is the most dominant color and we quantized
into one of the twelve top dominant colors and this is also very useful in especially in
shopping scenarios if somebody gives you
...this image of ...shoe and says it's...shoe and you want
to validate that this can be very useful in those cases and that's typically the cases where we use
it in bing a accent color as I talked about is the is the is
in color where we try a we use the get
...get the most saturated contrasting are popping color of the image and we try to
...wide skin tone and also if...unable to find any color then we use a default...column?
And, there are many interesting application once you get use a
bunch of start using this it's pretty addictive and bing we
...using it in various places whenever we show images.
So, for coming back to this example of this gentleman so that accent color which are
service returns currently is the color of his beard.
So, that's what was chosen.
Now I'm going to talk about a very important area which is addled and
receive detection.
When I say
addled what I really mean is pawn and this is and,
what racy means is these are images which wouldn't be suitable in
a school environment or it may not be suitable in certain cultures
...certain markets and you're working it's
...continuously improve all of these models of because we use it
and bing if you go to bing and if you choose strict mode you don't see adult
...not...images if you go to moderate mode you don't see
...images the...unc addled images?
So, what we do is as part of this service
redone you a label which says whether a particular images added or racy and
these labels...we think are the at the operating point of the...of
as the mostgives the best use experience but we also give you the actual
classified score so if you are building models on top of our models
a meta model you could use this chords and...your own classified on top of our
classifiers let's go a little bit more into detail about this so?
The first of all I would emphasize that are models are really robust and they've been
used in bing with a build with bing training data for many years and they use deep
neural networks it's very important to
...with the advantage of using deep...networks like, for example,
if there's a mother with a baby and a lot of skin and it won't be identified as an
adult because our dn models of learned that this is not...this is not addled.
And, also the second important point is that...flexible thresholds, for example,
there's a default operating point at which this classifier works
...it any classifier the a lot of false positives.
But, what you can do is you can say that I really don't want to have any
at adult documents in my application in that case you can go for the point a higher
recall point but if you go with...recall point we'll have more false positives and in that case you
will have to use human...filter them out on the other hand you can say that I just one...I don't
want to...anybody who is who may not be a of
like false negatives that in that case you'll end up having some leakage so
let's talk about this is a very important topics I just want to have one more slide to go into
details about this, for example, you had an
application where you at ten thousand images and on average there are two-point-six
person images adult which is pretty high two hundred sixty images are ten-k?
And, the simplest way would be you would have some person sitting there
...an example of the fran...application which I was talking about where fat
fans uploading images...have somebody sitting and watching all the ten thousand images very
quickly and trying to identify which
...but what you could do is you could to use us service and us add a
higher recall point and we will say that about
...three hundred fifty five of them...identified as
an adult and if you the judge who's sitting
there would focus on these three hundred fifty five and you would catch two hundred sixty two hundred eight out
of two hundred sixty images right away and you would identify them to be adult and they would be filtered
out from application obviously...I'm talking all this by just looking at the image
in most cases you have other context you have context like text like somebody
has said something about an image or people are typing in comments that helps obviously
helps you identify addled images then this history typically
users over using your...many years may not post
anything offensive and this context which is also important is, you know,
in some cases they might
...sudden scenarios people might tend to post more adult images.
Just to make this wind how do we do this in bing in bing what we do is we use
the same...the image classifier but we also
...which images this classifier this
prior on which page they are so we know the page information we know url information we
know domain information and that gives us context ofyou know,
whether a particular images adult in john and then any image which is at the boundary of the
threshold we use human judges for that and then we combine that with the query
...users typing the query classified and also how people engaging with this image
...typically...image people tend to click on it for any query so,
that the mixes...identify what
the so the meta point here is that one should if you have other signals besides
...signals please use them.
Now the next topic and we'll talk about is face detection so this was the
original image I showed you at the beginning of the presentation and we
identify the exact face location so
we're able to identify that there's a mail-in this is his is approximate
age and, what is the face rectangle of this image?
And, this
...very useful in many scenarios it's a very useful always to know...there are people in it
...most pictures almost fifty percent of the pictures are about people and if you knew how many people out
there that...a couple...one person in it you can do many interesting things.
And,...our face detection algorithm that does it can detect up to
sixty four people in it and just to make this point even the
thing there's a university of massachusetts at amherst has this face competition
of the microsoft dataset called the
fd db dataset which is which is used tomeasure how good your
face detection is an microsoft research is number one
...across all the competitions we have zero false positives on that
dataset and, recall of eighty-three percent...eighty three percent of those four-eighty party percent
of those photographs were able to identify faces and,
we never say something is a face which is
...office and this is better than the other two big combinators which
are name here the only two other companies which do face detection the
way we do okay and then the this and
...you have a detailed algorithm about-face searching and
face algorithms I didn't talk about thisbriefly just show you the website so we
have this project oxford website which is just announce couple of days back and
it has the face api xyz of complete module dedicated to face so if you
wanted to find out whetheryou could submit a set of photographs...can say
...fifty employees in my co you could submit photographs of those employees and then you can
send an photograph and say is it one of them so there's
of face verification...face...also you could give to
...these two people are the same person or not there's a set of speech api
...convert...speech into text
...into speech and the vision api is the talk I'm giving and then the lastly
...language understanding as well so this is the site project
oxford dot ai and all these demos are free and then there's also tear
...of free if you have as your subscription you could...could do so,...
first-year it's free...from the application so let's go back to my
...and then so, where do we use this so there was a
lot of talk yesterday if you have you been following the internet a about this
site which was based how do how old dot net so this vent very wide all once
...did his demo and this uses the same api
the face api and in this case if you try to estimate
the your exact age which is looks...lot of fun and you should all
...but the real application for an eml developer is with the way we use
it in bing is use it as a classifier we just put it as a feature to the of
feature to our model and we know what it helps as is your diaper query like?
...on...so you in this case you
want photographs of the younger medina and then what we do is we use this,
you know, all this photographs what age they are approximate age and
...it helps us make better relevance results so that's how we use it so it's
not about giving a precise age of a person but just a
using intelligently to identify a person is...or older or the
of one there's one percent in the pitch photograph for their multiple people in the photograph?
Yeah, and, then the lastly face detection is also
useful for thumbnail detection and I'll talk more about that later.
So, this first api...in summary it does
...detection category detection color image type and
face and if you have the flexibility also of getting all of
these features and if you only find some of them interesting you can just pick and choose which features interesting
to you now I'll walk over to the next topic which is ocr
...character recognition so one of our launch partners for all siard is art
...institute of artificial intelligence what they're trying to do is they're
building a artificial intelligence system which can answer
...questions for sixth-grade eight-grade and tenth grade eggs science exams
as in particular and for bad they need to understand example questions they need
to then explain those...the answers to those questions to their students.
And, for that the first step would be to actually do be able to read example questions one of the
challenges of example questions especially eight-grade science exams out
...of diagrams in eight-grade science exams and then the
needs to be a way you could interpret these images and extract
text out of them so let me show you a demo of how we solve this.
So, if you go to the same demo site we have ocr here so
what ocr does is obviously takes a image looks at the text on that image and it and it
converts that into machine usable character stream and if you look at
the detail what we redone is we are we what...doing here is...oughta detections
...able to recognize that this is english-language we also able to recognize that this all the taxes
...on a straight line
...text angle is zero and then we draw
bon bounding box on every line and every word so, you know,
exactly where the word is in the picture?
And, if you take another photograph like this one here the words
are a little bit tilted is a two degrees so what happens is the images taken
it straightened out and then all the text is extracted from it.
And, all the bounding boxes are given you can also select your
own image let me try a I could
tribe personal image as well I have this recipe done by my son so it
converts what he wrote on his you know,
he made a recipe for muffin and...it can convert it into text and
tell me exactly maybe not very useful but I'll show you very useful scenario which
...institute of artificial intelligence is using
what they're doing is they're taking this decks and now they know what exactly
...text in the science diagram and they can also find all the
...for it so they know exactly what the text is and this helps them
...what and,
then they using other features to figure out that this what kind of science diagram this
...and then the helps them in the obviously they have the
question also what the science question is and they can help answer the questions.
So, let's talk a little bit more about ocr.
So, all cr ...one thing about ocr is it's a very mature
technology it's being used across microsoft in many products one drive office
lengths one node bing and microsoft translator the new thing in this services the
to new things one thing is that this the first-time we have automatically detecting
a language and the second a so you could provide, you know,
it's very expensive to have twenty-one libraries on your machine so here it's all in the
cloud so it's very easy to have this the automatically detection
service available and the second aspect which is new
is cross platform the all of micros all of project oxford is
...cross platform that is if you have an ios app or android app you
can hit this service and you can take advantage that will siard eeoc
...library but theas far as functionalities concert the ocr library...ship with windows
stand is exactly the same its own the only two things which are different is...that library
works only with windows this with this service will work with any device and also
it does automatically, automatically detects languages and then we all if the decks
is stilted then we straighten it so that's and, then we give that information back
...so because of many times if you wanted to draw bounding boxes on the text which you
identified and you wanted to put that in the ux this aspect is very useful so
we if you have rotating imagine anyway we give that information back and then we
give bounding boxes for every text and every word...sorry every line and every line and every word.
And, this ...are...limitations one is that...
text is more than forty degrees then in that case of we don't know more rotation
then forty degrees and the quality of all seattle we don't publish any office shall pr because it
...it varies a lot on the type of content
to have if you have content which is a text focused images it will
do very well but if you have if you have text focus but if there's lot of course sieve
...the pr is going to not be as good and,...
photographs...text is just in the background it is not the dominant aspect the
false-positive...very different depending on the example also and I have not
shown you an example...different language so you could also take a language
I don't speak any of the other languages your chinese french or spanishabout
...you what here will do it is automatically detecting that is
chinese and it's able to show the output chinese,
chinese language and then it tells you that it is in chinese which is
very useful that itself could be a useful feature.
And, what we use it in bing I'm from
being team where we use it in bing is views it actually for
added detection as well so the topic I was talking about one of the biggest problems is the lot-of
quotes which are inappropriate so we are able to filter those output by using ocr?
So, this site in
...this service is a big say image you can provide a language or
default is auto-detects and if, you know,...text is a
...to provide orientation are also and the output is the language that text
angle and orientation as I said that text angle and orientation is useful
because you want to you might want to show you might want to draw ux around the words...the text.
And, then we provide bounding boxes for each a line...every word.
Ok, let me-let me want to our
third topic so this is talking about tom...service.
The...service is a very interesting problem so what happens
is most images out there are either landscape or portrait
but whenever there's a thumbnail it's always a squared thumbnail and what happens is you
take a landscape image or portrait image and then you...into a squared this is a very common
...which happens in across the many applications and
thisproblem even becomes much more complex because very
...you want to put these images on different devices on phone stabbed species
...the layouts are different and you don't want to store the same
comunale multiple times for multiple devices
or multiple scenarios what if there was a service which you took your image and,
you told them...the service which is the target
or target devices or tiger target container and it would and you the exact
right image for that scenario so that's exactly what the service does it takes
an image and it identifies what is the main object in that
image and then what we what we identify...grab the image to say this is the
region of interest it shouldn't be crop and then we re scaled
image to fit the target dimension this can be again understood bunch better with
...with the demo so you go back to us site and here have
...so this is the original image...person standing on top of
...mountain and what's happening is the original images
a landscape image and what we're
trying to do is try to fit this image in either in landscape these three a...the
...image and the last to...portrait images and obviously...used you can see this a
very big challenge to put a landscape image into a portrait container and even the
square container ideally this person should be in the center of the image and
...that would be the best thing so let...me turn right now this in this demo the smart cropping
is stand-off so if you don...on our smart cropping what...see is that...person in the
...images exactly in the middle and
in the landscape image what works for a
portrait to the last to portrait containers also pretty...so if you
don't offer you'll see that things are moving and then
...able to identify the region of interest let's take another
example this is a person reading a book in front of a fireplace and you're
right...smart cropping stoned on and as you can
see it looks pretty good but if you don
often smart dropping and just select the center of the imageagain,
this is a landscape image...work well for portrait but even if you look at the squared which is the most
popular comunale it doesn't look...good because the full it doesn't know
that the person is much more important than the fireplace?
And, the...more examples you can try let me try this let's
turn off the smart dropping and then try the logo the
logos very interesting because in logo
...all the content is important you should never crop
logo because all the information it's a loss of information if you crop and that's
why looks horrible here but when you do is when you turn on smarter
...cropping in this case what you see is what we have done is...instead of cropping the images we
...images because we know it's this text on the image and therefore you shouldn't cropped
images actually bad these images and therefore all of them just look
...scaled to fit even the smallest containers.
Ok.
So, let's.
Go back to the thumbnails service.
So, yeah,
so, the demo...showing is that of the original image was a three by two and
we're trying to fit it into different containers and in most cases
the thumbnails this-is just a illustration purposes we tried different containers but what
we're trying to optimize is four-square containers and that's the and
...thumbnails r squared.
So, this ...api is a very straightforward api you
take an image you give the dimensions of the target...you want to put the image and,
you would all the enable smart...just for you know, it's for fun but you
...normally cupid through because you one smart cropping and then the output would be
a thumbnail image which you can then use in the in your thing and we are
...thinking a lot of enhancements here once we know how much interested
that is in this kind of api because...this can before that optimized as well?
So, how can you take advantage of all of
these services so all of these services are available as restful
api and we also provide a simple sdk which wraps around
is restful api and the data that I speak is available for a android
...dicapta
...for dot net and the...the...which you can do
...very says ...if you go to asher you can get a subscription key of
...is free...nave...to certain number of transactions per month and you can
make a make write a few lines of code upload your local image and
...analyzing them and using application the kind of output you will get is what is at the...
you'll get this kind of output will tell you what kind of image it is all the...it's adult
...one of the scores for ed what is a category it belongs to and,
...information
so it's pretty straightforward to before you to use are service?
The three key reasons I would say you should tryout
...service we need we need this technology
in-house to our many of
our own microsoft applications especially being emits search and we you re
...continuously improving all of this all of these features which I talked about today.
And, because it's all about...service you always get the latest and the best at all times
and the third reason is that it is available as a cloud services
very easy to integrate its cross platform and you can use it in any application you want.
And, I've talked a lot about bing today why,
you know, being a start part about as and search engine but within microsoft bing is
being use...a variety of products as
an intelligent engine its use in office and many of the office new office features of
being intelligence and them windows and...on I uses a lot of bing xbox
...and now for the first-time
get exposing this technology as a service as part of project...oxford
so you can you get us developer can...direct advantage of this services.
I'd like to...the call to action for all of you is to go to our website trial website
outcry out all the demos...only images demos free for anybody to
...you can just upload images you can upload even...image from
an internet you can even type any image which you can even typing url if
...upload your image you can even type...url and,
the demos...don't store any images there was a lot of talk right now about
the that the...privacy concerns the none of the images a store and,
also we had if you're interested in knowing
what are the one of the other features we have as part of project oxford like speech
language understanding or face detection there was another session which happened two days
back you can watch that we have a dedicated boot on the third-floor
with lot-of exports there if you have more questions and then we have an active forum
which is which is a lot of people asking questions and also I'll take any questions right
now if you have...can come forward to the mike and ask questions thank you very much?
Could use the mike because getting recorded?
You have list of what's in the pipelining now so, yeah, I can talk about a couple of things so like
for category detection we are expanding of the number of categories people
want so it's only eighty-six categories we expanding that
...and we improve the quality that for...you have many interesting things
...should you re...image it normally miniature palmdale
...breezes interesting to have a url so what we could do it...the url of and
...give you a real-world example do you have something that would recognize a piece of
an image in an image yes that's the thing we are technology
...working on and, legion here is...that the
...that me and we are working on that technology which will hopefully at some later time
we can talk about that if we can talk about it now one-fifth something about that?
If that's his project so that's good question moi.
He's asking the whether you can detect box.
Given a small piece of an image can you look at other images and say this
piece is in those images are the technology called a...actually you want
to detect the...the...the oddly moi.
Production...
When...be available...rules example we have a number of customers
are waiting for that yet and we have yet ...work with you the when we have that
Because xerox warms to detect when top-secret photographs
or documents are being printed.
they want to be able to recognize pieces of images that areprohibited list,
yeah, exactly and people also want to...the copyright violation that's
...like if someone as an image which is they
...because...very...they want to be notified.
When should check because we are also working on that?
Brigade you can talk offline every disagree let's ask the question let's talk about.
Question with regard to the...over...
say with regard to the optimal imagery ...
Image resolution so for ocr you
...that the maximum dimension if you thousand six hundred right here so what
...other functionality like classifying.
...you have any kind of maximum them and she's yet that mathematician
...can...your we just...say some... of
...and...and believe...is the scale diametrically
fucked but you have any kind of optimum resolution which would say okay this.
No, I can do very well on...as well as optimum dimensions so,
basically they believe there should be off of it nobody high-quality the
...small but if it's...logical...of...be...the bandwidth.
...the question response time-code yahoo good...the...
I have to equation the first one is you also working on providing a
...a description of the image so we had a you presented the
category so it gives you the category but, for example, for the woman...a book with
a fireplace...focusing on maybe providing a woman is reading a book by
a fireplace text...from microsoft research that...published papers
...that and if you go to...today we also give you
...interesting information about an image of and, we have that
...roadmap recalling that dec insights get insights about the image and.
Description of...thanks and the second question is about the coping capabilities smart
cropping is your id to casual solace images so that you could
...some as some kind of proxy for websites all right so that's what we wanted
to what we want to do it that vone...there's no reason for you to store the
of...on your we return the...ideally what we should do...which is...return
...and then if you're calling from and iphone you would know that iphone
this is an iphone...high-resolution should give you even a better higher-quality
...and if you're...from a device which has low-resolution we should
...and that's how exactly how you that internally within microsoft no-kill you drive like...if
...such today...iphone the quality of the images are going to better because
the device...cannot handle the iconic images we don't...so that's an enhancement we can
do to this service andyou surely...thanks?
Videos oreos...that's.
A very good question actually that is one of the best
...enterprise scenarios security and
...detection so yes that's in our road map and,
I...a lot of when I was reading our customers...a lot of people often about
seen detection and, we have we have made some promises who...bing videos
...extract all the interesting images in...multiple images to
...make a story and...show what are the images
Customers want really is this is...and it's a security camera
...my house and dorm...me when you see my own
cash so that those kind of scenarios and, you know,
we are reacting networking or at least...that area.
Okay, I'll take any questions offline we go off-camera thank you.